

Contact Information

+380673416259

denis180984@gmail.com

Kalush, Ukraine

Telegram

Linkedin

GitHub

WhatsApp

Tech Skills

- HTML5/CSS3/SASS
- JavaScript
- Parcel
- Node.js
- SASS
- React

Soft Skills

- Teamwork
- Communicative
- Flexible
- Willingness to learn

Languages

English - Intermediate

Ukraine - native

DENIS BUKHTAROV

JUNIOR FRONTEND DEVELOPER

Summary

I would like to express my interest in applying for a full-time job in Front-End Developer in a company that's aimed at making both everyday life and business easier, more productive and user-friendly. I have sound knowledge of HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and React. Also, I have hands-on experience in following Agile /Scrum methodology when working in a team. I am a fast learner, responsible, and ready for challenging tasks.

Project Experience

FoodSta, <u>Link</u> [HTML, SASS, JS, Parcel] A website with a responsive layout. https://www.mey.and.developer.

Develop one section Offerings and daily mettings with team.

B: https://targbox.ru/blog/wp/link-whatsapp-telegram-viber-wp

WebStudio, <u>Link</u> [HTML, SASS, JS, Parcel] A website with a responsive layout. Role: developer.

Develop all section, Responsive Design vs. Adaptive Design, Flexbox

Home Number Six, <u>Link</u> [HTML, SASS, JS, Parcel] Role: developer. Java Script home work.

Work Experience

2016 - 2022

61, Olenu Pchilku St., Kalush, Ivano-Frankivsk region, Ukraine, 77300

Tornado Fight Club, Owner

- Provide the highest level of professional customer service, greets members, prospective members, guest and team
- Plan various engaging routines, music, and movements depending upon the type of class to balance healthcare with fun and motivating programs
- · Be available to work early mornings, evenings and weekends

2010 - 2016

1, Lisova, Kopanku, Ivano-Frankivsk region, Ukraine, 77300

GOODVALLEY, Buyer

- Developing an effective and accurate system for monitoring purchase orders
- Delivering a weekly purchase order report to supervisors that indicates the invoice number for all closed orders
- Assisting the Supply Chain Manager with maintaining inventory levels and materials on a regular basis

Education

IT School GoIT 2022- 2023 Fullstack Developer Ternopil National Economic University 2001 - 2006 Tne Banking System, Master's degree